[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which statement is a characteristic of a packet filtering firewall?",
    "choices": [
      "They are susceptible to IP spoofing.",
      "They examine each packet in the context of the state of a connection.",
      "They have a high impact on network performance.",
      "They filter fragmented packets."
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is one benefit of using a next-generation firewall rather than a stateful firewall?",
    "choices": [
      "integrated use of an intrusion prevention system (IPS)",
      "reactive protection against Internet threats",
      "support of logging",
      "support of TCP-based packet filtering"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What are two characteristics of an application gateway firewall? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "Performs most filtering and firewall control in software.",
      "Provides an integrated intrusion prevention and detection feature.",
      "Uses connection information maintained in a state table and analyzes traffic at OSI Layers 3, 4, and 5.",
      "Analyzes traffic at Layers 3, 4, 5 and 7 of the OSI model.",
      "Uses a simple policy table look-up to filter traffic based on Layer 3 and Layer 4 information."
    ],
    "answer": [0, 3],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What are two benefits of implementing a firewall in a network? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "A firewall will sanitize protocol flow.",
      "A firewall will inspect network traffic and forward traffic based solely on the Layer 2 Ethernet MAC address.",
      "A firewall will reduce security management complexity.",
      "A firewall will provide accessibility of applications and sensitive resources to external untrusted users.",
      "A firewall will prevent unauthorized traffic from being tunneled or hidden as legitimate traffic through an enterprise network."
    ],
    "answer": [0, 2],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which type of firewall is commonly part of a router firewall and allows or blocks traffic based on Layer 3 or 4 information?",
    "choices": [
      "proxy firewall",
      "next generation firewall",
      "stateful firewall",
      "packet filtering firewall"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which three layers of the OSI model include information that is commonly inspected by a stateful firewall? (Choose three.)",
    "choices": [
      "Layer 1",
      "Layer 2",
      "Layer 3",
      "Layer 4",
      "Layer 5",
      "Layer 7"
    ],
    "answer": [2, 3, 4],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which type of firewall is supported by most routers and is the easiest to implement?",
    "choices": [
      "application gateway firewall",
      "stateful firewall",
      "next generation firewall",
      "packet filtering firewall"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which type of firewall generally has a low impact on network performance?",
    "choices": [
      "stateless firewall",
      "application gateway firewall",
      "next generation firewall",
      "stateful firewall"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which two protocols are stateless and do not generate connection information needed to build a state table? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "ICMP",
      "UDP",
      "HTTP",
      "FTP",
      "TCP"
    ],
    "answer": [0, 1],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which type of traffic is usually blocked when implementing a demilitarized zone?",
    "choices": [
      "traffic originating from the DMZ network and traveling to the private network",
      "traffic that is returning from the public network and traveling to the DMZ network",
      "traffic originating from the private network and traveling to the DMZ network",
      "traffic that is returning from the DMZ network and traveling to the private network"
    ],
    "answer": 0,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "How does a firewall handle traffic that is originating from the DMZ network and traveling to a private network?",
    "choices": [
      "Traffic is usually allowed when it is originating from the DMZ network and traveling to a private network.",
      "Traffic is allowed when it is originating from the private network, but the response traffic from the DMZ network will be blocked.",
      "Traffic is usually blocked when it is originating from the DMZ network and traveling to a private network.",
      "Traffic is usually not filtered using firewall rules when it is originating from the DMZ network and traveling to a private network."
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "When implementing a ZPF, which statement describes a zone?",
    "choices": [
      "A zone is a group of one or more devices that provide backup and disaster recovery mechanisms.",
      "A zone is a group of administrative devices that protect against rogue access point installations.",
      "A zone is a group of hardened computers known as bastion hosts.",
      "A zone is a group of one or more interfaces that have similar functions or features."
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Firewall Technologies Quiz (15)"
  }
]
